When all is lost... miracles can happen
A Christmas Wish is a tv movie, family, drama film directed by Craig Clyde.
A broke single mother lands a job at a small town diner where the kindly
patrons and staff help her family to have a happy holiday.
Martha Evans, played by Kristy Swanson.
Les McCallum, played by Edward Herrmann.
Joe Hopkins, played by K.C. Clyde.
Clarice Miller, played by Aline Andrade.
Jeanie Bullington, played by Danielle Chuchran.
Trudy Willis, played by Tess Harper.
Mickey and Minnie Wish Upon a Christmas is a musical Christmas television
special released on December 2, 2021 on Disney Junior.
It is produced by Disney Television Animation.
It is the second spin-off special of Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up
Adventures after Mickey's Tale of Two Witches.
The film explores themes of prayer, holiday, diner, bullying, single mother.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.